{
    "subject": "resource/Martin_Smith_(Royal_Marines_officer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/militaryBranch",
    "object": "resource/Royal_Marines",
    "human_readable": "Martin Smith served in the Royal Marines.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9752857089042664,
            "question": "Was Martin Smith part of the Royal Marines?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9388999342918396,
            "question": "What does 'served in the Royal Marines' imply about Martin Smith?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8330540657043457,
            "question": "What military branch did Martin Smith serve in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8087612986564636,
            "question": "Who served in the Royal Marines?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5414761304855347,
            "question": "What kind of training would someone need to serve in the Royal Marines?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5313981175422668,
            "question": "Do you know any famous people who have served in the Royal Marines?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4711940884590149,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Martin Smith's military career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.366580605506897,
            "question": "What is Martin Smith's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3347039222717285,
            "question": "What are the Royal Marines known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3301195800304413,
            "question": "Is there any other information we know about Martin Smith besides his service?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Martin Smith served in the Royal Marines.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5666_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the Royal Marines known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5666_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Martin Smith's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5666_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Martin Smith's military career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5666_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5666_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5666_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5666_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5666_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5666_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5666_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5666_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5666_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5666_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5666_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents provide several mentions of Martin Smith, including his military career and positions held within the Royal Marines. For example, one document states that he was \"Commissioned in May 1984\" and another states that he succeeded Major General Ed Davis as Commandant General Royal Marines in June 2014. This information supports the triple that Martin Smith served in the Royal Marines."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Martin Smith joined the Royal Marines in 1984 and had a long military career within the organization, including various commands and roles. Therefore, the statement \"Martin Smith served in the Royal Marines\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}